<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Minimo</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../index.html</link>
	<description>TRAVEL BLOG</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 13:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../wp-content/uploads/2020/12/favicon.ico</url>
	<title>Minimo</title>
	<link>./../../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Spain requires all visitors to have a proof negative PCR test taken</title>
		<link>./../2020/12/11/spain-requires-all-visitors-to-have-a-proof-negative-pcr-test-taken/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../2020/12/11/spain-requires-all-visitors-to-have-a-proof-negative-pcr-test-taken/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 13:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFESTYLE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=192</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[According to many reports, this initiative can stimulate economic growth, improve the experiences of tourists and increase revenue. At the moment,&#160;Spain requires all visitors to have a proof negative PCR test&#160;taken no more than 72 hours before departure. The date to allow travelers to enter without any restrictions is set for the end of March. &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../2020/12/11/spain-requires-all-visitors-to-have-a-proof-negative-pcr-test-taken/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Spain requires all visitors to have a proof negative PCR test taken</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>According to many reports, this initiative can stimulate economic growth, improve the experiences of tourists and increase revenue.</p>



<p>At the moment,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.travelinglifestyle.net/canary-islands-remain-open-for-tourism-but-require-pcr-tests/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Spain requires all visitors to have a proof negative PCR test</a>&nbsp;taken no more than 72 hours before departure. The date to allow travelers to enter without any restrictions is set for the end of March.</p>



<p>Currently, a governmental organization is managing a marketing campaign that has a total cost of more than $2.3 million. Several experts have indicated that the initiative could attract millions of tourists, and throughout the next month, at least 25 percent of guests may visit the Canary Islands.Evaluating Various Types of Statistics</p>



<p>During 2019, more than 21 million tourists visited the Balearic Islands, and according to multiple reports, 37 percent of these visitors chose luxury hotels. Since January 2020, less than 1.9 million tourists have visited the Balearic Islands. The epidemic has affected local businesses, thousands of workers, large airlines and countless restaurants.Visiting Beautiful Islands and Enjoying Many Activities</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.travelinglifestyle.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/spain-to-waive-travel-restrictions.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Several reports have suggested that approximately 820,000 tourists may travel to the Canary Islands during the next month. Recently, a well-known business has indicated that the company will open 11 luxury hotels in December 2020. When tourists visit the Canary Islands, the guests will not quarantine themselves, and typically, the visitors can enjoy snorkeling, boating, diving and hiking.Learning Additional Information and Examining Important Updates</p>



<p>Before travelers make reservations, the tourists can visit a well-known&nbsp;<a href="https://www.spain.info/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">website</a>&nbsp;that provides important news, and the guests could evaluate various discounts, enjoyable activities, local attractions and detailed schedules.</p>



<p>When the tourists browse the website, the visitors could also make reservations, contact a travel agency and evaluate numerous services.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../2020/12/11/spain-requires-all-visitors-to-have-a-proof-negative-pcr-test-taken/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hot spring pools offer plentiful therapeutic benefits.</title>
		<link>./../2020/12/11/hot-spring-pools-offer-plentiful-therapeutic-benefits/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../2020/12/11/hot-spring-pools-offer-plentiful-therapeutic-benefits/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 13:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFESTYLE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=190</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nature&#160;is a lot more mesmerizing when it lets us embrace the serenity along with filling our hearts with joy.&#160;Hot spring pools&#160;are one such way of having the best time, and making our soul feel soothed, and escaping from the normal hassles of life. Hot&#160;spring pools&#160;offer plentiful therapeutic benefits. From boosting the blood circulation of the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../2020/12/11/hot-spring-pools-offer-plentiful-therapeutic-benefits/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Hot spring pools offer plentiful therapeutic benefits.</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Nature</strong>&nbsp;is a lot more mesmerizing when it lets us embrace the serenity along with filling our hearts with joy.&nbsp;<strong>Hot spring pools</strong>&nbsp;are one such way of having the best time, and making our soul feel soothed, and escaping from the normal hassles of life.</p>



<p>Hot&nbsp;<strong>spring pools</strong>&nbsp;offer plentiful therapeutic benefits. From boosting the blood circulation of the body to helping one feel stress-free, they comprise the power to heal and fascinate the living being.</p>



<p>Other than a natural phenomenon, hot spring pools with amazing sights are the best place to have a day-out with your loved ones. So, if you are a big-time wanderer, then read on for&nbsp;<strong>5 natural spring pools</strong>&nbsp;around the world.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/img_5fcfacb7841fe.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The Blue Lagoon, Iceland</p>



<p>The&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Lagoon_(geothermal_spa)#:~:text=The%20Blue%20Lagoon%20(Icelandic%3A%20Bl%C3%A1a,nearby%20Svartsengi%20geothermal%20power%20station." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Blue Lagoon</a>&nbsp;in Iceland is one of the&nbsp;<strong>most popular springs</strong>&nbsp;in the world with a view no less than heaven. Surroundings spilled over with blue color and water that flutters between 98 to 102 degree Fahrenheit makes it one of the picturesque places to have a whale of a time.</p>



<p>Be it any season of the month, you can have a dip in the water to refresh your mind and body. This is because minerals present in the water help to boost your skin health and eliminate toxins from the body. All you need to make a booking in advance and a little enthusiasm to enjoy nature.Pamukkale Thermal Pool, Turkey</p>



<p>If experiencing heaven on the Earth is one of your bucket-list wishes, then Pamukkale&nbsp;<strong>thermal pool</strong>&nbsp;in Turkey is picture-perfect. Located in Pamukkale, the Cotton Castle town, this spring is not merely a place to wander, but also to cherish the beauty of history and culture.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It was formed over several centuries, the top of which lies the memorial of the Roman city of Hierapolis. The water temperature of the pool ranges from 95 to 212 degrees Fahrenheit, and it is tenfold during the off-season, that is November and March when the air starts to chill.Takaragawa Onsen, Japan</p>



<p>Located in Minakami city, Takaragawa is the magical&nbsp;<strong>spring pool</strong>&nbsp;to blow away the cobwebs. Other than the majestic view, it offers bounteous healing benefits and can let you embrace the serenity of nature with the surroundings mix of forest and mountains.&nbsp;</p>



<p>You can dip into the hot water, or you can ski with full swing on visiting this wondrous hot water spring in Japan. To a little more surprise, you can double your blissfulness by enjoying the grilled fish and delicious pickles served in the nearby hotels.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So, don’t miss the chance to live in the moments of serenity at the place where you can bathe, sleep, and eat like there is no tomorrow.Khir Ganga, India</p>



<p>If in your life, you haven’t been to a place where you can get rid of pain and aches along with making your heart feel delighted, make a plan to visit Khir Ganga in India.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It’s one of the heavenly&nbsp;<a href="https://storyv.com/hot-springs-in-bali/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>hot water springs</strong></a>&nbsp;located in the state of Himachal Pradesh and has been in the lives of people for centuries.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Even though it takes four hours to hike up to this place, once reached, you can make yourselves feel like you are hugging nature. Besides, the healing power of water is worth your endeavors as it soothes your muscle and foot ache in no time.&nbsp;Chena Hot Spring, Alaska</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/img_5fcfacbb7d3af.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The place where one can experience the soaking pleasure in life with a full heart is&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chena_Hot_Springs,_Alaska" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>Chena</strong>&nbsp;<strong>Hot</strong>&nbsp;<strong>Spring</strong></a>&nbsp;in Alaska. Considered as the ravishing handsel of nature, it is the amazing hot water spring with water hovering at 106 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>



<p>The best time to visit the destination is between August and April, where other than a dip in the water, you can relish the fun activities with your loved ones.&nbsp;Conclusion</p>



<p>Life is a one time opportunity and there is no chance that we can miss living it to the fullest. Therefore, take some time out of your hectic life and experience heaven on Earth by tripping to your favorite natural hot&nbsp;<strong>spring</strong>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../2020/12/11/hot-spring-pools-offer-plentiful-therapeutic-benefits/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states</title>
		<link>./../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTODIARY]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The&#160;Pacific Coast Ranges&#160;are a series of mountains that can be found along the coast of the United States and a few other North American countries. These ranges are also referred to as the North American Cordillera or the Western Cordillera.&#160; The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states and&#160;North American countries, including Canada and northern &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The&nbsp;<strong>Pacific Coast Ranges</strong>&nbsp;are a series of mountains that can be found along the coast of the United States and a few other North American countries. These ranges are also referred to as the North American Cordillera or the Western Cordillera.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states and&nbsp;<strong>North American countries</strong>, including Canada and northern Mexico. As we will discuss later on, a few of the largest and most famous mountain ranges in the world form part of this series.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you are interested in visiting one or a few of these&nbsp;<strong>incredible mountain ranges</strong>, you have come to the right place. In this article, we will be mentioning everything that there is to know about the Pacific Coast Ranges.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/54f168efa2099b606847db4a2b212cd0_1.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Image Source: WikipediaThe Pacific Coast Ranges</p>



<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pacific_Coast_Ranges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The Pacific Coast Ranges</a>&nbsp;make up a considerable part of North America. As we have already mentioned, parts of these mountain ranges can be found on the western coast of the&nbsp;<strong>United States, Canada, and even northern Mexico</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>To be more specific, the Coast Ranges occupy about 4500 miles of the United States coastline and run roughly 1000 miles into Canada.</p>



<p>We already know that a few of the largest and most well-known mountain ranges in the states form part of the Pacific Coast Ranges, including the&nbsp;<strong>Rocky Mountains</strong>, Columbia Mountains, and Interior Mountains. More so, this series is made up of multiple basins and plateaus.</p>



<p>Seeing as though the series of mountain ranges spread across different territories and countries, the&nbsp;<strong>characteristics</strong>&nbsp;of each group of mountains varies. For example, if you visit the mountains in Alaska, you will find stunning tidewater glaciers.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, if you prefer warmer climates and decide to visit the Southern California ranges, you will be met with&nbsp;<strong>mild and dry climates</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/69e51c7e2afe0102d0e3d52bc5b9dc61_3.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Image Source: Visit CaliforniaWhy Are These Ranges Such A Special Travel Destination?</p>



<p>If you are the type of person who enjoys&nbsp;<strong>hiking, camping, climbing, mountaineering, skiing, or simply being in the outdoors</strong>, you may want to check out the Pacific Coast Ranges. There are various adventurous activities that you can part-take in when touring these beautiful mountains.&nbsp;</p>



<p>With that being said, it is recommended that you decide what type of trip you are looking for before you embark on your journey. As we now know, the various sections of this series of mountains can be found in&nbsp;<strong>differing climates</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So, if you do not mind the cold, you may want to visit the mountains in Alaska or Canada. On the other hand, if you prefer warmer weather, the ranges in the United States or Mexico may be the better choice for you.&nbsp;</p>



<p>There are various reasons as to why these mountains are so&nbsp;<strong>special</strong>&nbsp;for tourists. If you have ever visited one of the ranges, you are sure to remember it for its natural beauty and stunning views.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In fact, hundreds of thousands of tourists from all over the world come to North America simply to take in the scenery that these mountains deliver.&nbsp;What Can You Expect To See Near The Pacific Coast Ranges?</p>



<p>If you are planning a trip to the Pacific Coast Mountains, there is plenty for you to see and do while on your adventure. For example, if you go during the right time of year, you will be able to swim in one (or more) of the thousands of&nbsp;<strong>lakes</strong>&nbsp;that can be found in the mountain ranges.&nbsp;</p>



<p>On top of the stunning water bodies, there is plenty of&nbsp;<strong>wildlife</strong>&nbsp;to look out for. For example, the mountain ranges in the United States are home to elk, moose, deer, mountain goats, black bears, grizzly bears, wolves, and bobcats.&nbsp;</p>



<p>With that being said, the wildlife that you can expect to see will depend on the specific mountain range that you visit.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/8dc1e171b23673b9906b0a2e443a0604_2.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Image Source: WikipediaSummary</p>



<p><a href="https://kids.britannica.com/students/article/Pacific-Coast-Ranges/276241" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The Pacific Coast Ranges</a>&nbsp;are made up of a&nbsp;<strong>series of mountain ranges</strong>&nbsp;that can be found across Northern America. A few of the world’s largest and most famous ranges, including the Rocky Mountains, form part of this very popular tourist attraction.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you are to visit the Pacific Coast Ranges, you can expect to see beautiful scenery, including&nbsp;<strong>natural lakes and</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover These Natural Spring Pools Around the World</title>
		<link>./../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTODIARY]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nature&#160;is a lot more mesmerizing when it lets us embrace the serenity along with filling our hearts with joy.&#160;Hot spring pools&#160;are one such way of having the best time, and making our soul feel soothed, and escaping from the normal hassles of life. Hot&#160;spring pools&#160;offer plentiful therapeutic benefits. From boosting the blood circulation of the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Discover These Natural Spring Pools Around the World</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Nature</strong>&nbsp;is a lot more mesmerizing when it lets us embrace the serenity along with filling our hearts with joy.&nbsp;<strong>Hot spring pools</strong>&nbsp;are one such way of having the best time, and making our soul feel soothed, and escaping from the normal hassles of life.</p>



<p>Hot&nbsp;<strong>spring pools</strong>&nbsp;offer plentiful therapeutic benefits. From boosting the blood circulation of the body to helping one feel stress-free, they comprise the power to heal and fascinate the living being.</p>



<p>Other than a natural phenomenon, hot spring pools with amazing sights are the best place to have a day-out with your loved ones. So, if you are a big-time wanderer, then read on for&nbsp;<strong>5 natural spring pools</strong>&nbsp;around the world.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/img_5fcfacb7841fe.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The Blue Lagoon, Iceland</p>



<p>The&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Lagoon_(geothermal_spa)#:~:text=The%20Blue%20Lagoon%20(Icelandic%3A%20Bl%C3%A1a,nearby%20Svartsengi%20geothermal%20power%20station." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Blue Lagoon</a>&nbsp;in Iceland is one of the&nbsp;<strong>most popular springs</strong>&nbsp;in the world with a view no less than heaven. Surroundings spilled over with blue color and water that flutters between 98 to 102 degree Fahrenheit makes it one of the picturesque places to have a whale of a time.</p>



<p>Be it any season of the month, you can have a dip in the water to refresh your mind and body. This is because minerals present in the water help to boost your skin health and eliminate toxins from the body. All you need to make a booking in advance and a little enthusiasm to enjoy nature.Pamukkale Thermal Pool, Turkey</p>



<p>If experiencing heaven on the Earth is one of your bucket-list wishes, then Pamukkale&nbsp;<strong>thermal pool</strong>&nbsp;in Turkey is picture-perfect. Located in Pamukkale, the Cotton Castle town, this spring is not merely a place to wander, but also to cherish the beauty of history and culture.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It was formed over several centuries, the top of which lies the memorial of the Roman city of Hierapolis. The water temperature of the pool ranges from 95 to 212 degrees Fahrenheit, and it is tenfold during the off-season, that is November and March when the air starts to chill.Takaragawa Onsen, Japan</p>



<p>Located in Minakami city, Takaragawa is the magical&nbsp;<strong>spring pool</strong>&nbsp;to blow away the cobwebs. Other than the majestic view, it offers bounteous healing benefits and can let you embrace the serenity of nature with the surroundings mix of forest and mountains.&nbsp;</p>



<p>You can dip into the hot water, or you can ski with full swing on visiting this wondrous hot water spring in Japan. To a little more surprise, you can double your blissfulness by enjoying the grilled fish and delicious pickles served in the nearby hotels.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So, don’t miss the chance to live in the moments of serenity at the place where you can bathe, sleep, and eat like there is no tomorrow.Khir Ganga, India</p>



<p>If in your life, you haven’t been to a place where you can get rid of pain and aches along with making your heart feel delighted, make a plan to visit Khir Ganga in India.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It’s one of the heavenly&nbsp;<a href="https://storyv.com/hot-springs-in-bali/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>hot water springs</strong></a>&nbsp;located in the state of Himachal Pradesh and has been in the lives of people for centuries.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Even though it takes four hours to hike up to this place, once reached, you can make yourselves feel like you are hugging nature. Besides, the healing power of water is worth your endeavors as it soothes your muscle and foot ache in no time.&nbsp;Chena Hot Spring, Alaska</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flydubai is making flights during the COVID-19 pandemic</title>
		<link>./../2020/12/11/flydubai-is-making-flights-during-the-covid-19-pandemic/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../2020/12/11/flydubai-is-making-flights-during-the-covid-19-pandemic/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFESTYLE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Flydubai is making flights during the COVID-19 pandemic a little easier for passengers around the world. Health expenses and quarantine costs are covered if the passenger is diagnosed while traveling between September 1 and December 31, 2020.How the COVID-19 Flight Coverage Works The global coverage is a free feature of any ticket booked through the&#160;Flydubai &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../2020/12/11/flydubai-is-making-flights-during-the-covid-19-pandemic/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Flydubai is making flights during the COVID-19 pandemic</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Flydubai is making flights during the COVID-19 pandemic a little easier for passengers around the world. Health expenses and quarantine costs are covered if the passenger is diagnosed while traveling between September 1 and December 31, 2020.How the COVID-19 Flight Coverage Works</p>



<p>The global coverage is a free feature of any ticket booked through the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.flydubai.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Flydubai website</a>&nbsp;or mobile app. It also covers if the ticket is booked through a travel agent, a Flydubai travel shop or the company’s customer center.</p>



<p>This coverage lasts for 31 days after the first flight included on the itinerary. Even if the passenger continues to travel to another city, coverage remains intact.</p>



<p>Travelers are able to enjoy a comfortable, safe trip without any unforeseen problems. If diagnosed with COVID-19 while traveling, Flydubai covers the first 150,000 euros of medical expenses.</p>



<p>In addition, some of the quarantine costs are covered as well. If a passenger is placed in quarantine, Flydubai covers up to 100 euros of quarantine expenses per day.Flydubai Makes It Easier to Travel During the COVID-19 Pandemic</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.travelinglifestyle.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/flydubai-free-covid-insurance-1024x683.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Other than offering global coverage to passengers, Flydubai is also taking other steps to protect passengers during the pandemic. In September, the company announced that passengers would be eligible for&nbsp;<a href="https://www.flydubai.com/en/plan/covid-19/pcr-test-reduced-rates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">discounted COVID-19 PCR tests</a>.</p>



<p>Passengers only have to submit their booking confirmation and identification to get a discounted test. The test results are normally available within 48 hours, but special clinics can provide results in 24 hours.</p>



<p>Thanks to these efforts, Flydubai is now able to resume normal operations. In late November, the airline achieved its first scheduled commercial flight from Dubai to Tel Aviv.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../2020/12/11/flydubai-is-making-flights-during-the-covid-19-pandemic/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bali and Japan planning to open a travel bubble for tourism</title>
		<link>./../2020/12/11/bali-and-japan-planning-to-open-a-travel-bubble-for-tourism/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../2020/12/11/bali-and-japan-planning-to-open-a-travel-bubble-for-tourism/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFESTYLE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bali is now ready to begin safely receiving tourists. On Dec. 7, The governor, I Wayan Koster, held a virtual meeting with Indonesia’s Ambassador of Japan and President Director of Garuda Indonesia Airlines. The purpose was to help Indonesia and Japan agree on safety protocols for travel between the two countries. Koster stated that Bali &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../2020/12/11/bali-and-japan-planning-to-open-a-travel-bubble-for-tourism/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Bali and Japan planning to open a travel bubble for tourism</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bali is now ready to begin safely receiving tourists. On Dec. 7, The governor, I Wayan Koster, held a virtual meeting with Indonesia’s Ambassador of Japan and President Director of Garuda Indonesia Airlines.</p>



<p>The purpose was to help Indonesia and Japan agree on safety protocols for travel between the two countries.</p>



<p>Koster stated that Bali has created a task force for the covid-19 pandemic. Along with supervising travel regulations, the task force will also ensure businesses within the country are operating in a safe manner.From Japan to Bali: Flying Without Layovers</p>



<p>A survey showed that 80 percent of Japanese residents would choose Bali as a travel destination. Since the demand is high, Garuda may soon begin operating a direct flight between the two countries.</p>



<p>As of now, it appears that Bali will soon be reopening its doors to Japan. Ida Bagus Made Bimantara, the Director of Europe International Affairs Minister, announced that the Balinese government will continue working to ensure local hotels, restaurants, and other hospitality businesses meet all required safety regulations.Japan and Bali: Safety During Covid-19</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.travelinglifestyle.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/bali-japan-bubble-819x1024.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>During the first quarter of 2020, foreign tourism was down in Bali by 22 percent. However, the Balinese people have fared well in the battle against covid-19.</p>



<p>The culture may have played a role in controlling the spread. It centers around tight-knit village communities. When the community elders suggest staying home and keeping safe, the community listens.</p>



<p><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/may/22/from-near-disaster-to-success-story-how-japan-has-tackled-coronavirus" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Japan is another covid-19 success story</a>, and it too may have the local culture to thank. Wearing masks was common in Japan long before the pandemic. Other practices, such as bowing rather than shaking hands, may have played a role.</p>



<p>Japan is also known for its hermit culture. It’s estimated there are more than half a million Japanese “hikikomori,” a term that refers to a person who chooses a reclusive lifestyle. The hikikomori often refuses to leave home for years at a time. Unhealthy as this is, it may have helped control the virus.</p>



<p>The post&nbsp;<a href="https://www.travelinglifestyle.net/bali-and-japan-planning-to-open-a-travel-bubble-for-tourism/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bali and Japan planning to open a travel bubble for tourism</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../2020/12/11/bali-and-japan-planning-to-open-a-travel-bubble-for-tourism/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
