<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>PHOTODIARY &#8211; Minimo</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../../index.html</link>
	<description>TRAVEL BLOG</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:58:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../../../wp-content/uploads/2020/12/favicon.ico</url>
	<title>PHOTODIARY &#8211; Minimo</title>
	<link>./../../../../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states</title>
		<link>./../../../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTODIARY]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The&#160;Pacific Coast Ranges&#160;are a series of mountains that can be found along the coast of the United States and a few other North American countries. These ranges are also referred to as the North American Cordillera or the Western Cordillera.&#160; The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states and&#160;North American countries, including Canada and northern &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The&nbsp;<strong>Pacific Coast Ranges</strong>&nbsp;are a series of mountains that can be found along the coast of the United States and a few other North American countries. These ranges are also referred to as the North American Cordillera or the Western Cordillera.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The Pacific Coast Ranges occupy various American states and&nbsp;<strong>North American countries</strong>, including Canada and northern Mexico. As we will discuss later on, a few of the largest and most famous mountain ranges in the world form part of this series.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you are interested in visiting one or a few of these&nbsp;<strong>incredible mountain ranges</strong>, you have come to the right place. In this article, we will be mentioning everything that there is to know about the Pacific Coast Ranges.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/54f168efa2099b606847db4a2b212cd0_1.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Image Source: WikipediaThe Pacific Coast Ranges</p>



<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pacific_Coast_Ranges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The Pacific Coast Ranges</a>&nbsp;make up a considerable part of North America. As we have already mentioned, parts of these mountain ranges can be found on the western coast of the&nbsp;<strong>United States, Canada, and even northern Mexico</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>To be more specific, the Coast Ranges occupy about 4500 miles of the United States coastline and run roughly 1000 miles into Canada.</p>



<p>We already know that a few of the largest and most well-known mountain ranges in the states form part of the Pacific Coast Ranges, including the&nbsp;<strong>Rocky Mountains</strong>, Columbia Mountains, and Interior Mountains. More so, this series is made up of multiple basins and plateaus.</p>



<p>Seeing as though the series of mountain ranges spread across different territories and countries, the&nbsp;<strong>characteristics</strong>&nbsp;of each group of mountains varies. For example, if you visit the mountains in Alaska, you will find stunning tidewater glaciers.&nbsp;</p>



<p>However, if you prefer warmer climates and decide to visit the Southern California ranges, you will be met with&nbsp;<strong>mild and dry climates</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/69e51c7e2afe0102d0e3d52bc5b9dc61_3.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Image Source: Visit CaliforniaWhy Are These Ranges Such A Special Travel Destination?</p>



<p>If you are the type of person who enjoys&nbsp;<strong>hiking, camping, climbing, mountaineering, skiing, or simply being in the outdoors</strong>, you may want to check out the Pacific Coast Ranges. There are various adventurous activities that you can part-take in when touring these beautiful mountains.&nbsp;</p>



<p>With that being said, it is recommended that you decide what type of trip you are looking for before you embark on your journey. As we now know, the various sections of this series of mountains can be found in&nbsp;<strong>differing climates</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So, if you do not mind the cold, you may want to visit the mountains in Alaska or Canada. On the other hand, if you prefer warmer weather, the ranges in the United States or Mexico may be the better choice for you.&nbsp;</p>



<p>There are various reasons as to why these mountains are so&nbsp;<strong>special</strong>&nbsp;for tourists. If you have ever visited one of the ranges, you are sure to remember it for its natural beauty and stunning views.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In fact, hundreds of thousands of tourists from all over the world come to North America simply to take in the scenery that these mountains deliver.&nbsp;What Can You Expect To See Near The Pacific Coast Ranges?</p>



<p>If you are planning a trip to the Pacific Coast Mountains, there is plenty for you to see and do while on your adventure. For example, if you go during the right time of year, you will be able to swim in one (or more) of the thousands of&nbsp;<strong>lakes</strong>&nbsp;that can be found in the mountain ranges.&nbsp;</p>



<p>On top of the stunning water bodies, there is plenty of&nbsp;<strong>wildlife</strong>&nbsp;to look out for. For example, the mountain ranges in the United States are home to elk, moose, deer, mountain goats, black bears, grizzly bears, wolves, and bobcats.&nbsp;</p>



<p>With that being said, the wildlife that you can expect to see will depend on the specific mountain range that you visit.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/8dc1e171b23673b9906b0a2e443a0604_2.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Image Source: WikipediaSummary</p>



<p><a href="https://kids.britannica.com/students/article/Pacific-Coast-Ranges/276241" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The Pacific Coast Ranges</a>&nbsp;are made up of a&nbsp;<strong>series of mountain ranges</strong>&nbsp;that can be found across Northern America. A few of the world’s largest and most famous ranges, including the Rocky Mountains, form part of this very popular tourist attraction.&nbsp;</p>



<p>If you are to visit the Pacific Coast Ranges, you can expect to see beautiful scenery, including&nbsp;<strong>natural lakes and</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2020/12/11/the-pacific-coast-ranges-occupy-various-american-states/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover These Natural Spring Pools Around the World</title>
		<link>./../../../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 11:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PHOTODIARY]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nature&#160;is a lot more mesmerizing when it lets us embrace the serenity along with filling our hearts with joy.&#160;Hot spring pools&#160;are one such way of having the best time, and making our soul feel soothed, and escaping from the normal hassles of life. Hot&#160;spring pools&#160;offer plentiful therapeutic benefits. From boosting the blood circulation of the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="./../../../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/index.html"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Discover These Natural Spring Pools Around the World</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Nature</strong>&nbsp;is a lot more mesmerizing when it lets us embrace the serenity along with filling our hearts with joy.&nbsp;<strong>Hot spring pools</strong>&nbsp;are one such way of having the best time, and making our soul feel soothed, and escaping from the normal hassles of life.</p>



<p>Hot&nbsp;<strong>spring pools</strong>&nbsp;offer plentiful therapeutic benefits. From boosting the blood circulation of the body to helping one feel stress-free, they comprise the power to heal and fascinate the living being.</p>



<p>Other than a natural phenomenon, hot spring pools with amazing sights are the best place to have a day-out with your loved ones. So, if you are a big-time wanderer, then read on for&nbsp;<strong>5 natural spring pools</strong>&nbsp;around the world.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://storyv.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/img_5fcfacb7841fe.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The Blue Lagoon, Iceland</p>



<p>The&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Lagoon_(geothermal_spa)#:~:text=The%20Blue%20Lagoon%20(Icelandic%3A%20Bl%C3%A1a,nearby%20Svartsengi%20geothermal%20power%20station." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Blue Lagoon</a>&nbsp;in Iceland is one of the&nbsp;<strong>most popular springs</strong>&nbsp;in the world with a view no less than heaven. Surroundings spilled over with blue color and water that flutters between 98 to 102 degree Fahrenheit makes it one of the picturesque places to have a whale of a time.</p>



<p>Be it any season of the month, you can have a dip in the water to refresh your mind and body. This is because minerals present in the water help to boost your skin health and eliminate toxins from the body. All you need to make a booking in advance and a little enthusiasm to enjoy nature.Pamukkale Thermal Pool, Turkey</p>



<p>If experiencing heaven on the Earth is one of your bucket-list wishes, then Pamukkale&nbsp;<strong>thermal pool</strong>&nbsp;in Turkey is picture-perfect. Located in Pamukkale, the Cotton Castle town, this spring is not merely a place to wander, but also to cherish the beauty of history and culture.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It was formed over several centuries, the top of which lies the memorial of the Roman city of Hierapolis. The water temperature of the pool ranges from 95 to 212 degrees Fahrenheit, and it is tenfold during the off-season, that is November and March when the air starts to chill.Takaragawa Onsen, Japan</p>



<p>Located in Minakami city, Takaragawa is the magical&nbsp;<strong>spring pool</strong>&nbsp;to blow away the cobwebs. Other than the majestic view, it offers bounteous healing benefits and can let you embrace the serenity of nature with the surroundings mix of forest and mountains.&nbsp;</p>



<p>You can dip into the hot water, or you can ski with full swing on visiting this wondrous hot water spring in Japan. To a little more surprise, you can double your blissfulness by enjoying the grilled fish and delicious pickles served in the nearby hotels.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So, don’t miss the chance to live in the moments of serenity at the place where you can bathe, sleep, and eat like there is no tomorrow.Khir Ganga, India</p>



<p>If in your life, you haven’t been to a place where you can get rid of pain and aches along with making your heart feel delighted, make a plan to visit Khir Ganga in India.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It’s one of the heavenly&nbsp;<a href="https://storyv.com/hot-springs-in-bali/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>hot water springs</strong></a>&nbsp;located in the state of Himachal Pradesh and has been in the lives of people for centuries.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Even though it takes four hours to hike up to this place, once reached, you can make yourselves feel like you are hugging nature. Besides, the healing power of water is worth your endeavors as it soothes your muscle and foot ache in no time.&nbsp;Chena Hot Spring, Alaska</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2020/12/11/discover-these-natural-spring-pools-around-the-world/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
